<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Analyst skills on Notebook</title>
    <link>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/analyst-skills/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Analyst skills on Notebook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/analyst-skills/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Team Types</title>
      <link>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/analyst-skills/team_types/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/analyst-skills/team_types/</guid>
      <description>Team types #  Summary #  Broadly, we might think of three types of analytic team within the ICS:
 Performance Data analysis/ reporting Data science  The roles of these teams is discussed in more detail following.
Performance #  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Training</title>
      <link>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/analyst-skills/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/analyst-skills/training/</guid>
      <description>Training #  Within this piece of work the following training needs have been identified:
 TODO  A summary of available training in these areas follows.
Area one #   TODO  Appendix A: Training providers #   AphA Health Education England Government Statistics Service NHS R Community Midlands Decision Support Network FutureNHS Healthcare Evaluation Data Kurtosis Skills Development Network Operational Research Society QA EDX WiseOwl FutureLearn Laria Udemy Jumping Rivers Population Health Exchange NIHR CLAHRC North Thames Faculty of Public Health Public Health England East Midlands AHSN Strategy Unit Software carpentry PenARC Mango  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Competency Frameworks</title>
      <link>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/analyst-skills/competency-frameworks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/analyst-skills/competency-frameworks/</guid>
      <description>Competency frameworks #  Introduction #  APHA carried out a review of competency frameworks for health service analysts, published in 2021. There were 28 competency frameworks considered in the review, of which 10 were found to contain significant detail about analytical job roles and career progression. Some of the material from this review and from the competency frameworks is presented below.
They assessed four frameworks as being the highest ranked in the scoring that they designed:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
