<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on Notebook</title>
    <link>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on Notebook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Analyst skills</title>
      <link>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/analyst-skills/_intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/analyst-skills/_intro/</guid>
      <description>Analyst skills #  I&amp;rsquo;m looking at the issue of analyst skills in the Nottinghamshire ICS with some other people at the moment. The brief is:
 Identify a generic set of skills for healthcare analysts in the region Identify extra skills necessary dependent on role and organisation Identify individuals within the ICS who can provide training on these skillsets Identify gaps where the system is not self sufficient for training and procure training (preferring free training) Look at the range of external training available to the system Identify areas of training need that cannot be met internally or externally  This will quite obviously require a very large amount of information about analyst skills, careers, and training, and so I will be making notes as I go along here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Competency Frameworks</title>
      <link>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/analyst-skills/competency-frameworks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/analyst-skills/competency-frameworks/</guid>
      <description>Competency frameworks #  Introduction #  APHA carried out a review of competency frameworks for health service analysts, published in 2021. There were 28 competency frameworks considered in the review, of which 10 were found to contain significant detail about analytical job roles and career progression. Some of the material from this review and from the competency frameworks is presented below.
They assessed four frameworks as being the highest ranked in the scoring that they designed:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
