<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Goldacre Review on Notebook</title>
    <link>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/goldacre_review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Goldacre Review on Notebook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/goldacre_review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Modernising Service Analytics</title>
      <link>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/goldacre_review/modernising_service_analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/goldacre_review/modernising_service_analytics/</guid>
      <description>Modernising NHS service analytics #  Summary of recommendations #  [TBC]
Introduction #  &amp;ldquo;At present there is no formal professional body (but some outstanding grass roots organisations); very little formal structure around teaching and training, or ‘continuing professional development’; and a general lack of clear technical job descriptions or qualifications specific to NHS service analytics that managers without technical skills can use to evaluate the skills mix that they have, or need, in their service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusted Research Environments</title>
      <link>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/goldacre_review/tre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/goldacre_review/tre/</guid>
      <description>What is a &amp;ldquo;Trusted Research Environment&amp;rdquo;? #   In outline, a Trusted Research Environment (TRE) is a secure environment that researchers enter in order to work on the data remotely, rather than downloading it onto their own local machine. Users can extract and download the answers from their analyses – such as results tables, or graphs – but individual patients’ data always stays within the secure environment
 &amp;ldquo;good TREs can also provide a more efficient and collaborative computational environment for all data users, and an opportunity to make modern open working methods the simple default.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Working</title>
      <link>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/goldacre_review/open-working/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/goldacre_review/open-working/</guid>
      <description>Open working #  For more information about open source and software licensing in the NHS see elsewhere in this notebook.
Myths about open working #  This section starts with mythbusting, which is very welcome because there is a lot of rubbish spoken about open code in the NHS. To summarise:
 Adopting open working practices does not mean other countries or industry can exploit intellectual property created with state funds: there should be a robust and thoughtful exceptions framework to impose commercial licenses or restrictions on review and (separately) re-use of publicly funded code, where this is actively helpful; but this closed approach should be used in a planned and deliberate fashion, where it meets national strategic objectives, not as the unplanned default approach</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/goldacre_review/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/goldacre_review/privacy/</guid>
      <description>The challenge of privacy in health data #  High quality analysis requires very detailed information about individuals, which means that a group of analysts have &amp;ldquo;access to every recorded detail, of every medical event, for almost every citizen, all the way back to birth&amp;rdquo; (I&amp;rsquo;m a little dubious of this claim myself. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure anyone could give you this even for the patients in my Trust, limiting themselves only to events within the Trust).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nottinghamshire Healthcare NHS Trust</title>
      <link>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/goldacre_review/nottshc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/goldacre_review/nottshc/</guid>
      <description>What should Nottinghamshire Healthcare NHS Trust do #  Nottinghamshire Healthcare NHS Trust (NHC) is part of an analytically able ICS and employs three analytical teams with good working relationships: Applied Information, Performance, and CDU data science. The teams combine expertise in data curation and management, performance and quality surveillance, and data science methods and analytical pipelines.
NHC could become one of the &amp;ldquo;data pioneer&amp;rdquo; trusts (or form part of a &amp;ldquo;data pioneer&amp;rdquo; ICS) that the report recommends in NHSA 7 by building on the work already happening at the trust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What has NHS-R done and what else should it do?</title>
      <link>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/goldacre_review/nhs-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/goldacre_review/nhs-r/</guid>
      <description>Where does NHS-R fit? #  Brilliantly, NHS-R is already leading on many of the things from this review that are important to me. I&amp;rsquo;m going to highlight the stuff we already started doing, with nobody asking us to, and a paltry amount of funding, and then I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk about the stuff that we can make a really solid contribution to tomorrow if we&amp;rsquo;re brought in to the conversation (which, according to the review, we should be).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Further Work</title>
      <link>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/goldacre_review/further-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisbeeley.github.io/notebook/docs/goldacre_review/further-work/</guid>
      <description>Further work #  I love this review and it&amp;rsquo;s probably the best blueprint for real change that I&amp;rsquo;ve seen, although it&amp;rsquo;s worth mentioning that I&amp;rsquo;ve seen 10+ such documents that have not led to real change, not because of deficiencies on their part but because of ignorance, apathy, and unchecked commercial interests that have pushed methodologically inferior and expensive tools and methods to senior managers who don&amp;rsquo;t know what they&amp;rsquo;re buying.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
